export const data = [
  {
    id: '1',
    name: 'English Reading Assignment 1 (A1)',
    level: 'Beginner',
    Title: 'Lucy\'s Day',
    readingText: "Lucy is a young girl. She lives in a small town with her family. Lucy has one brother and one sister. Her brother’s name is Sam, and her sister’s name is Lily. Lucy likes to play outside. She loves the green trees and the blue sky. Every morning, Lucy eats breakfast with her family. She drinks milk and eats bread. After breakfast, she goes to school. At school, Lucy learns English and plays with her friends. She is happy and loves her family very much.",
    audioFiles: ['/Sounds/LucyTest.mp3', '/Sounds/LucyTest.mp3', '/Sounds/LucyTest.mp3', '/Sounds/LucyTest.mp3'],
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Where does Lucy live?",
        choices: ["In a big city", "In a small town", "On a farm", "In a village"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "How many brothers and sisters does Lucy have?",
        choices: ["Two brothers", "One brother and one sister", "One sister only", "Two sisters"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What is Lucy's brother’s name?",
        choices: ["Lily", "Lucy", "Sam", "Tom"],
        correctAnswer: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "What does Lucy love to do outside?",
        choices: ["Run and jump", "Play outside", "Dance", "Sing"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What color is the sky that Lucy loves?",
        choices: ["Green", "Blue", "Red", "Yellow"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What does Lucy drink for breakfast?",
        choices: ["Water", "Juice", "Tea", "Milk"],
        correctAnswer: 3,
      },
      {
        question: "What does Lucy eat with her milk?",
        choices: ["Rice", "Bread", "Fruit", "Cake"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "Where does Lucy go after breakfast?",
        choices: ["To the park", "To school", "To play", "To the market"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What does Lucy learn at school?",
        choices: ["Math and Science", "Music and Dance", "English", "Cooking"],
        correctAnswer: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "How does Lucy feel about her family?",
        choices: ["Angry", "Happy", "Sad", "Confused"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
      },
    ],
  },
]
